

FULL STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CLAYTON PARROS

BIO

Highly motivated full stack software engineer certified by the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill. Experience working with both the front end and back end of applications. Excellent project management skills, team skills, and communication.

CONTACT

Mobile: 973-570-7918 Celparros@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/cparros/ https://github.com/cparros

PROJECTS

- Mentor Me (Current Project)
 - http://mentorme3000.herokuapp .com/
- Football Data Visualization
 - https://cparros.github.io/football
 -visualization project/https://cparros.github.io/
 football-visualization-project/
- Workout Buddy
 - https://github.com/cparros/proje ct-2

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA CHAPEL HILL

Certificate in Full-Stack Software Engineering, 2021

• Graduation May 2021

Bachelor of Exercise Sports Science, 2013

- Leader of Distinction In the Carolina Leadership Academy
- · Captain of Track and Field Team
- All American Sprinter

SKILLS

- · Languages: HTML CSS, Javascript
- Tools: React, Node.js, Express, MySQL, MongoDB Bootstrap, Tailwinds, Github
- Web API experience
- Working knowledge of D3, Charts.js, and Tableau for data visualization

WORK EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL CONSULTANT/FE SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- VClubs Project | 2021 Present
- Provide feedback and guidance regarding tools and hardware
- Meet with dev team to discuss progress and milestones

FREELANCE SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Self | 2019 - Present

 Contributed to various projects working primarily in front end development but also some backend development

ASSISTANT COACH

The University of Mount Olive | 2017-Present

- Managed a large group of athletes
- Worked with individuals from both domestic and international backgrounds
- Liaison between multiple team captains/leaders, and the university Athletic Department

SHIFT MANAGER

Omega Sports | 2016-2018

- Supervised a staff of 8 employees
- In over 2 years was responsible for over \$500k In sales

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Professional Athlete

Nike/Adidas 2013-2016

- World Champion
- Team USA Member
- Olympic trials participant